io-media.com 2019-02-13

# Privacy Policy | IOMEDIA

### IOMEDIA - privacy statement

At IOMEDIA, we are committed to protecting your privacy and to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this statement of privacy explains data collection, use, and safeguarding information in those situations. Please read the complete IOMEDIA privacy statement.

### IOMEDIA – INFORMATION COLLECTION

If you browse IOMEDIA's website, you do so anonymously. We don't collect personal information - including your email address in any unsolicited manner. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which parts of our website you visit and how long you spend there. The only other information automatically provided to us is the type of computer and operating system you are using. Your browser supplies us with this information.

At times we may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, such as your email address and postal address, for purposes such as corresponding with us, registering at a IOMEDIA site, or registering a new IOMEDIA product. When you register with IOMEDIA, for example, we would collect the serial number of the software you licensed, your name, address, and email address.

All other products and company names mentioned in the IOMEDIA Web site may be trademarks of their respective owners.

Use of the IOMEDIA Logo for commercial purposes without the prior written consent of IOMEDIA may constitute trademark infringement and unfair competition in violation of federal and state laws. Use of any other IOMEDIA trademark in commerce may be prohibited by law except by express license from IOMEDIA.

### IOMEDIA – INFORMATION USE

If you provide us with your email or postal address, or have done so in the past, we will ask you if we can use it to send you updates on the latest IOMEDIA products and promotions. When you supply IOMEDIA with your personal information, we may use it to register your product, configure your system, or assist you with connecting to the Internet or Project Extranet. We may also use information that you have given us to contact you so that we may learn more about our customers. This will help us to develop better products and services. We may use your personal information to inform you about new products, services, and offers that may be of interest to you. These offers may be based on the information you provided in your initial transaction with us or in surveys.

### IOMEDIA – DECLINING EMAIL

IOMEDIA provides customers with an easy means to decline to receive email newsletters. Although most customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these opportunities, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may request to discontinue receiving these newsletters from us by simply replying to the email and informing us of your preferences. All email newsletters that you receive from IOMEDIA will tell you how to decline further email newsletters.

### IOMEDIA – PRIVACY

IOMEDIA's privacy policy is subject to change at any time.

IOMEDIA's website contains links to other websites and is not responsible for privacy practices of those websites. IOMEDIA encourages users to learn about the privacy practices of those websites.

### IOMEDIA

Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.

IOMEDIA is headquartered at:

640 West 28th Street, 9th Floor, New York, NY 10001

Tel: (212) 352-1115

Fax: (212) 352-1117
